export const roadData = [
    {
        question: "What should you do when you approach a red traffic light?",
        option1: "Speed up and quickly cross the intersection",
        option2: "Stop and wait for the light to turn green",
        option3: "Slow down and proceed with caution",
        option4: "Honk your horn to alert others",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a solid yellow line on the road indicate?",
        option1: "No overtaking or passing",
        option2: "One-way traffic",
        option3: "Pedestrian crossing zone",
        option4: "Parking area",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "When should you use your vehicle's hazard lights?",
        option1: "When you are double-parked",
        option2: "When you want to indicate a lane change",
        option3: "During an emergency or breakdown",
        option4: "When driving at night",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the maximum speed limit on highways?",
        option1: "60 km/h",
        option2: "80 km/h",
        option3: "100 km/h",
        option4: "120 km/h",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "When should you use your vehicle's fog lights?",
        option1: "During heavy rain",
        option2: "When driving in foggy conditions",
        option3: "At night to enhance visibility",
        option4: "Fog lights are not necessary",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a triangular road sign indicate?",
        option1: "Give way or yield",
        option2: "No entry",
        option3: "Stop ahead",
        option4: "Speed limit",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What should you do when you approach a roundabout?",
        option1: "Speed up to enter the roundabout quickly",
        option2: "Always give way to vehicles on the roundabout",
        option3: "Honk your horn to indicate your presence",
        option4: "Ignore the roundabout and continue straight",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the maximum blood alcohol concentration (BAC) limit for professional drivers?",
        option1: "0.02%",
        option2: "0.05%",
        option3: "0.08%",
        option4: "0.10%",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a blue circular road sign indicate?",
        option1: "Hospital ahead",
        option2: "Mandatory direction",
        option3: "Tourist attraction",
        option4: "Speed limit",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "When should you use your vehicle's high beam headlights?",
        option1: "Within city limits",
        option2: "In heavy traffic",
        option3: "When driving in well-lit areas",
        option4: "When driving on dark, unlit roads",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a solid white line on the road indicate?",
        option1: "No overtaking or passing",
        option2: "One-way traffic",
        option3: "Pedestrian crossing zone",
        option4: "Parking area",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What should you do when you encounter livestock on the road?",
        option1: "Speed up to avoid them",
        option2: "Flash your headlights to scare them away",
        option3: "Slow down and proceed with caution",
        option4: "Sound your horn continuously",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the maximum speed limit in urban areas?",
        option1: "40 km/h",
        option2: "60 km/h",
        option3: "80 km/h",
        option4: "100 km/h",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a rectangular road sign indicate?",
        option1: "Give way or yield",
        option2: "No entry",
        option3: "Stop ahead",
        option4: "Speed limit",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What should you do when you see a pedestrian waiting at a zebra crossing?",
        option1: "Speed up to cross the road before the pedestrian",
        option2: "Stop and allow the pedestrian to cross",
        option3: "Swerve around the pedestrian to avoid stopping",
        option4: "Honk your horn to indicate yourpresence",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a yellow rectangular road sign indicate?",
        option1: "Give way or yield",
        option2: "No entry",
        option3: "Stop ahead",
        option4: "Speed limit",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What should you do when you approach a railway crossing with flashing lights?",
        option1: "Speed up to cross the tracks before the train arrives",
        option2: "Stop and wait for the train to pass",
        option3: "Sound your horn to alert the train",
        option4: "Ignore the flashing lights and continue driving",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a red circular road sign indicate?",
        option1: "Hospital ahead",
        option2: "Mandatory direction",
        option3: "Tourist attraction",
        option4: "Stop",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What should you do when you see a traffic officer giving hand signals at an intersection?",
        option1: "Ignore the hand signals and proceed as usual",
        option2: "Follow the hand signals given by the officer",
        option3: "Honk your horn to attract the officer's attention",
        option4: "Change lanes to avoid the officer",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a green circular road sign indicate?",
        option1: "Hospital ahead",
        option2: "Mandatory direction",
        option3: "Tourist attraction",
        option4: "Speed limit",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a black circular road sign with a white line across it indicate?",
        option1: "No overtaking or passing",
        option2: "One-way traffic",
        option3: "Pedestrian crossing zone",
        option4: "Parking area",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What should you do when you approach a school zone?",
        option1: "Increase your speed to clear the zone quickly",
        option2: "Sound your horn to alert the students",
        option3: "Slow down and watch for children",
        option4: "Ignore the school zone if there are no students present",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a rectangular road sign with a white arrow on a blue background indicate?",
        option1: "Give way or yield",
        option2: "No entry",
        option3: "One-way traffic",
        option4: "Speed limit",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What should you do when you approach a road construction zone?",
        option1: "Speed up to clear the zone quickly",
        option2: "Follow the instructions given by the construction workers",
        option3: "Ignore the construction zone and continue driving",
        option4: "Sound your horn to alert the workers",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does a rectangular road sign with a red border indicate?",
        option1: "Give way or yield",
        option2: "No entry",
        option3: "One-way traffic",
        option4: "Speed limit",
        ans: 2,
    },
   
];